<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Masiz Pamoja</string>
    <string name="logo">Logo</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="no_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot your Password?</string>
    <string name="sign_in_statement">Already have an Account?</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="your_email">Email</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full names</string>
    <string name="hint_for_user">e.g. 0700000000</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="more_info">More Information</string>
    <string name="who_are_we">Who are we...?</string>
    <string name="what_do_we_do">What do we do....?</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="occupation">Occupation</string>
    <string name="issue_title">Title of  Issue</string>
    <string name="getPhoto">Add Photo</string>
    <string name="Done">done</string>
    <string name="message">Message : </string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="enter_name_error">Enter a name</string>
    <string name="enter_email_error">Enter an email</string>
    <string name="enter_password_error">Enter a password</string>
    <string name="invalid_email_address_error">Enter a valid email</string>
    <string name="error_occurred">Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="recent_blogs">Recent Blogs</string>
    <string name="take_photo">take_photo</string>
    <string name="subject">Subject :</string>
    <string name="event_photo">Event photo</string>
    <string name="this_is_the_name_of_the_event">This is the name of the event</string>
    <string name="about_event_title">About Event</string>
    <string name="date">date</string>
    <string name="no_tickets_for_this_event">No tickets for this event</string>
    <string name="_12_09_2019">12-09-2019</string>
    <string name="title_event">Title event</string>
    <string name="details_of_the_event">Details of the event</string>
    <string name="who_are_we_description">We are an organization focused in unifying and connecting women to information and services designed to address the growing concern on matters affecting women such as Gender based violence and Sexual and Reproductive Health rights (SRHR).</string>
    <string name="be_part_of_us">Be Part Of US</string>
    <string name="our_core_values">Our Core Values</string>
    <string name="core_values">.Trust .Empathy .Support .Integrity .Boldness</string>
    <string name="mission">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="mission_values">To provide a platform that informs, voices, connects, supports and solves the health dilemmas, social evils, and pave way for justice for the various affected women.</string>
    <string name="vision">Our Vision</string>
    <string name="vision_values">To be an established network within and without Kenya constantly providing credible information, empowerment and be the most trusted solution provider.</string>
    <string name="what_we_do_">Masiz Pamoja begun as an idea of a way to give a voice to the voiceless women in the society, especially after we realised that a lot of evils, such as rape, gender based violence etc. went unnoticed or unmentioned in society. These delicate matters require proper addressing channels to ensure the safety of the victims both physically, psychologically and emotionally.</string>
    <string name="what_we_do_1">Women in the country don’t have enough information to guide their choices and decisions related to sexual health issues. The world is saturated with information with no assurance of its credibility, making choosing difficult. Some issues are still considered taboo, making talking about them difficult in society e.g. family planning, unplanned pregnancies, abortions, rape, gender based violence, gynaecological services, HIV/AIDS etc. Women are not fully exposed to such services, which are important in ensuring a woman\'s healthy life style. Most women don\'t even know where to access these services, their importance, where to go to and most importantly we assume the cost to be so high to afford.  We aim to ensure that women get the right information and the right quality services by partnering with the right stakeholders, the government, the Ministry of Health, the NGOs addressing the various issues, the police and local agencies e.g. gynaecologist association of Kenya and the communications service providers.</string>
    <string name="what_we_do_2">Our aim is to act as a hub for recovery, encouragement and a new dawn for all the souls affected by various social injustices. We aim to connect women to information, guidance and counselling, encouragement, support, relief and a familial sense of belonging.  Our desire is to make more help convenient: from the police to the hospital, and therefore ensure full help, justice and closure; delivering mentorship, by linking victims and conquers with the right guidance and support allows for a self-supporting community which is key to maintaining consistency during the recovery process.  We all face different challenges every day and we come up with different solutions that work for us. Imagine combining and sharing all this knowledge to help our sisters all over the world solve and handle different situations.  This is our dream. A world where women are all heard and seen.</string>
    <string name="help_contacts">Help Contacts</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="CurrentPassword">Current Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="write_a_message">Write a message</string>
    <string name="prompt_message">Message...</string>


    <string name="connect">Connected</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnected, Please check your internet connection</string>
    <string name="error_connect">Failed to connect</string>

    <!-- messages -->
    <string name="message_welcome">Welcome to Socket.IO Chat –</string>
    <plurals name="message_participants">
        <item quantity="one">there\'s %d participant</item>
        <item quantity="other">there are %d participants</item>
    </plurals>
    <string name="message_user_joined">%s joined</string>
    <string name="message_user_left">%s left</string>
    <string name="user_action_typing">is typing</string>
</resources>
